<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TikTonic</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="push_up">\tStart on your hands and knees on a yoga mat on the floor, with your hands resting slightly wider than the width of your shoulders. Straighten your legs out behind you so you’re being supported by your hands and the balls of your feet. Keep your body in a straight line from the top of your head to your heels (holding your head up in line with your spine). Bend your elbows and lower your chest until it nearly touches the mat. Pause and then push yourself back up to the starting position. Beginner modification: Complete the push-up with your knees on the floor</string>
    <string name="push_up_shuffle">\tComplete a push-up (either on your knees or with your legs extended behind you, depending on your fitness level). Then, keep your core engaged and shuffle your right hand and right foot a step to the right side. Bring your left hand and foot to meet them. Complete another push-up there. Return to center and repeat on the opposite side. One set is five shuffles in each direction.</string>
    <string name="push_squeeze">\tStand with your hands in front of you with a 90-degree bend in your elbows. Hold your hands together and squeeze your chest as hard as you can. Hold the tension for up to 30 seconds and release; that’s one rep.</string>
    <string name="arms_triceps">\tSit in front of a bench or the end of a couch with your legs extended out in front of you away from the furniture. Position your hands on top of the furniture behind you with your hands about shoulder-width apart and your fingertips pointing toward your body. Straighten your arms and pull your body up so it is hovering over the floor. Then engage your triceps muscles as you bend your elbows until they’re at about a 90-degree angle. Press down from your hands and straighten your arms to return to the starting position. You should be supporting most of your body’s weight in your arms to get the greatest benefit from the move. To make the exercise easier, keep your knees bent at a 90-degree angle. One set is 12 reps.</string>
    <string name="arms_plank">\tGet into a plank position on the floor: Your hands should be on the mat with your shoulders directly above them, legs extended straight back behind you, toes on the mat, and your body forming a straight line from top of head to heels. Lower your left elbow down to the mat and then lower your right elbow down to the mat so you’re now in a forearm plank. Keep your core engaged and your body in a straight line. Push up and straighten your right arm. Then straighten your left arm as well. Repeat for 30 seconds, switching off which arm goes first; that’s one set.</string>
    <string name="arms_triangle">\tSettle into a plank position but place your hands close together under your chest and form a triangle with your index fingers and your thumbs (your thumbs should be in a straight line forming the bottom side of the triangle). Lower your chest toward the floor as if you were doing a regular push-up, keeping your elbows close to your body. Pause at the bottom and then push off the floor to return to the starting position. Modify by completing the push-up with your knees on the floor or by moving your hands slightly wider than the triangle shape. One set is 12 reps</string>
    <string name="back_supery">\tLie facedown on a mat with your arms extended in a Y position overhead and your legs are extended directly behind you on the mat. Using your back and shoulders, lift your chest and arms off the mat. Hold and then lower into the starting position. One set is 15 reps.</string>
    <string name="back_bird_dog">\tPosition yourself on your hands and knees on your mat with hands beneath your shoulders and your knees beneath your hips. While keeping your core engaged and stable, raise your right arm straight in front of you and extend your left leg straight out behind you, reaching both away from the body at the same time so both are parallel to the floor. Hold, engaging the hamstrings and glutes; then bring your arm and leg back to center. Repeat with your left arm and right leg. Complete 15 reps on each side for one set.</string>
    <string name="back_supert">\tLie facedown on a mat with your arms extended out to your sides so your body is in a T position. Using your back and shoulders, lift your chest and arms off the mat. Hold and then lower into the starting position. One set is 15 reps.</string>
</resources>